Ask us about ✔ room reservations [Contact Sales](https://www.trumba.com/connect/eventcalendar/contact_sales.aspx)

×

Fine Print
==========

Privacy Policy
==============

###### Last Revised: February 21, 2024

Trumba Corporation (“**Trumba**”) provides and hosts for its clients (“Clients,” or “you) customizable web calendars including event promotion and registration tools. When you use the calendar functionality, Trumba also makes available to you online calendar, scheduling, reminder, event information and publishing, and email and text messaging services. Together, the calendar functionality and the additional functionalities offered on client calendars shall be referred to as the “Services,” which may be accessed directly from the Trumba website or through your web sites when you publish online calendars.

This Privacy Policy explains how Trumba collects, uses and discloses information when you use our Services or otherwise interact with us. In order for you to make use of Services, you will need to register for an account. If you register for a personal account, where you are the only intended user of the calendar, please note that personal accounts are not intended for and should not be used by Clients in the European Economic Area (“EEA”). If you sign up for an account and you intend to allow others, such as your customers or end users to use the calendar services, you have an enterprise account and are considered to be an enterprise user.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you.

When we use the term “**Personal Information**” we mean any information that identifies an individual, such as (but not limited to) an individual’s name, email address, postal address, device-specific information and log information (as described below). Any information that does not, on its own, identify an individual person is considered and treated as non-personal information. When non-personal information is combined with other information so that it does or can be used to identify an individual, this information is treated as Personal Information.

Collection of Information
-------------------------

### Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the Services, request customer support, register for a free trial, subscribe to or use our Services, sign up for email and text message notifications, subscribe to other notifications, register for an event, sync your personal calendar with a Client Calendar, apply for a job, fill out an online form, create or update a calendar or submit a comment or complaint. We may collect your name, phone number, email address and other contact information, as well as information about your organization and role that you choose to provide to us. You may also provide us with credit card information in connection with payment for subscriptions, events and other purchases through the Site, which is only used to process the transaction.

The types of information we may collect includes Personal Information about you and any other information you choose to provide. We, or a designated third party, may collect payment and credit card information when you subscribe to our paid Services or purchase additional services.

### Information About Your Use of the Services

#### Usage Information

We collect information about your use of the Services, such as the ways in which you use our calendars or the ways in which you use our calendars to interact with your end users (if you are an enterprise user), the way you respond to us when we send you emails or communications or your preferences when you interact with our Services.

#### Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

* **Log Information**: We log information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address, your general location and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
* **Device Information**: We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system, and version.
* **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**: We and our service providers use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see the "Your Choices" section below.

#### Security

Security procedures, including encryption, are in place to protect the confidentiality of your data.

### Integrations with Other Technologies

You may have the option of integrating our Services with other services, technologies or platforms on your desktop and permitted websites. For example, you may choose to sync your calendar with another calendar you use for other services. These integrations may require you to input Personal Information or access or use Personal Information. These integrations may (i) check for updates automatically and transmit information about you to their server and/or engine; (ii) send information entered into or accessed by the technology to its server and/or engine and (iii) be visible to the public if embedded on publicly available webpages (such as social networking webpages), depending on the policies of that website.

Use of Information About You
----------------------------

We use the information we collect to provide, maintain and improve our Services, such as to administer your account, administer your calendar, and to provide you with insights to help you optimize your use of calendars.

We may also use the information we collect to:

* Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you transaction-related information, including confirmations and invoices,
* Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
* Send you notifications, reminders, event information, process registrations, integrate with your other calendars (at your request), and to allow you to register for events;
* Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
* Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by Trumba, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
* Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
* Detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of Trumba and others;
* Personalize and improve the Services; and
* Carry out any other purpose described to you when information about you was collected.

Sharing of Information About You
--------------------------------

We often need to engage third-party companies and individuals (such as payment processors, research companies and analytics and security providers) to help us operate and provide the Services. These third parties only have limited access to information about you, may use information about you only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated to us not to disclose or use information about you for other purposes.

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this privacy policy:

* With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf and provide the services you request;
* In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;
* If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Trumba or others;
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company;
* Between and among Trumba and our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and other companies under common control and ownership; and
* With your consent or at your direction.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

### Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others

We may allow others to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, and links clicked. This information may be used by Trumba to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity on our Services. For more information about these analytics services, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for these purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices).

Retaining Information About You
-------------------------------

Trumba will retain information about you only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy or as described to you, for as long as your account is active (i.e., for the lifetime of your Trumba account), or as needed to provide the Services to you. If you no longer want Trumba to use information about you to provide the Services to you, you may cancel your account. If you choose to close your account, Trumba may still retain and use information about you to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain information about you to comply with applicable tax/revenue laws), resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, and in accordance with our standard data deletion periods based on our system settings. We also retain log files for internal analysis purposes. These log files are generally retained for a limited period of time, except in cases where they are used for the safety and security of the Services, to improve functionality of the Services or we are legally obligated to retain them for longer time periods.

Transfer of Information About You to the U.S. or Other Countries
----------------------------------------------------------------

In order to provide you with the Services you subscribe to or that you request from us, your Personal Information will be transferred to the United States as that is where Trumba is based. In some cases, Personal Information about you may be transferred to or accessed from other countries outside the United States, including when you consent and allow us to do so, where it is required in order for us to provide Services to you and when we need to do so to provide functions like product support, troubleshooting and gaining insights into the usage patterns of our Services. When Personal Information about you is transferred to the United States and other countries, you may not have the same rights and protections as you do under local law. Any international transfers of Personal Information will be done in accordance with applicable law.

Your Choices
------------

### Account Information

You may update, correct or delete information about you at any time by logging into your online account or emailing us at privacy@corp.Trumba.com. If you wish to cancel your account, please email us at privacy@corp.Trumba.com, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Trumba by following the instructions in those emails or by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any of our emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy@corp.Trumba.com or mail us at:

Trumba Corporation  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
2442 NW Market St., #863  
Seattle, WA 98107  

#### Start creating and publishing your events today.

30-day free trial. No credit card required.

#### Connect with us.

1-800-925-0388 (M-F 9AM-5PM PT)

#### Features

#### Pricing

#### Resources

#### Our Company

#### Fine Print

#### What's New

#### Join Us!

©2004-2024 Trumba Corporation. All rights reserved. Trumba is a registered trademark of Trumba Corporation.
